Elika Gloria Marcus

Penultimate Accounting Student

Hard working and passionate accouting student with multiple internship experiences. I also has several skills in all different field in finance, audit and tax. I'm also flexible and adaptive to work as a team as well as working under pressure.

elikagloria18@gmail.com

+6287741849838

Indonesia

linkedin.com/in/elika-gloria-marcus in

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Accounting - Tax

Binus University

08/2018 - Present

GPA 3.37

WORK EXPERIENCE

Finance Intern

Kredit Utama Fintech Indonesia

02/2023 - 05/2023

Jakarta. Indonesia

Licensed and supervised by OJK Technology financial company whose mission is to facilitate loan access by utilizing technology.

Tasks

- Journal Input with Accurate
- Filing

Accounting Intern

Surya Semesta Internusa

09/2022 - 11/2022

Jakarta, Indonesia

Indonesian publicly traded construction company operating in 3 related sectors: property development and management, construction and hospitality.

Tasks

- Constructing Accounting and Financial Journal
- Constructing Tax Journal
- Bank Reconciliation

Finance Intern

Owens-Illinois (O-I)

02/2021 - 08/2022

Jakarta, Indonesia

One of the world's leading manufacturers of packaging products and it is currently the largest manufacturer of glass containers in several continents.

Tasks

- Monthly Tax Calculation, Reporting & Documentation
- Account Reconciliation
- Month End Closing (SAP & Hyperion)
- Cost Controlling, Budget & Forecast Process
- Financial Statement Review

Tax Volunteer

Direktorat Jendral Pajak (DJP)

02/2020 - 03/2020

Jakarta, Indonesia

Indonesian government agency responsible for formulating and implementing taxation policies and technical standardization in the field of taxation.

Achievements/Tasks

- Provide support for Taxpayer
- Master of Ceremony for Accounting Events

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Final Year Research (09/2022 - Present)

 Title: Analisis Hukum Benford Dalam Mendeteksi Kecurangan Laporan Keuangan Pada Perusahaan Manufaktur Sektor Industri Barang Konsumsi Yang Terdaftar Di Bei Pada Tahun 2017-2021

ORGANIZATIONS

Himpunan Mahasiswa Akuntansi (HIMA) (2018 - 2019)

CERTIFICATES

Brevet AB Participants (02/2022)

Training for different aspects of Tax including Personal and Corporate

LANGUAGES

Indonesian E
Native or Bilingual Proficiency F

English

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Tax Audit Accounting Finance

Accounts Receivable Accounts Payable